Bonus Short Stories

Your Warmth

The time was early morning, with less than a week having gone by since Rio began living with Miharu, Aki, and Masato.

Rio was sitting on the sofa in the living room of the rock, house, asleep. While there was no one else in the room with him at first, early riser would eventually appear — it was Miharu.

When she noticed him on the sofa, she tried to greet him cheerfully. “Ah, Haruto. Good morning...?” However, she soon noticed something was off about him, and her voice trailed off immediately. She approached hesitantly, noticing how papers were scattered across the table. On them were neatly organized graphs of letters and sentences.

This is... for us...?

Miharu could guess what the purpose of those papers were: they were language learning materials made for herself and the other two Japanese students. There was no mistaking it, as there were explanations of the Strahl grammar and vocabulary written on it in Japanese.

Rio must have stayed up late — or perhaps gotten up early — in order to create the learning materials for them. It made Miharu feel a bit apologetic towards him.

“Zzz... Zzz...”

Rio was sleeping peacefully with an expression that still held a sort of childish innocence.

He normally seems so mature, but he’s actually the same age as me, huh... Though he said he was a university student in his past life…

Because of Rio’s ability to fly through the air and runat inhuman speeds, an outsider might think of him as superhuman... but someone like him could seemingly still feel tired, as well as sleep looking like this.

Miharu looked at Rio closely, examining him. He really did have a pretty face, she thought. Then, as she was looking at his appearance —

I wonder where Haru-kun is now?

A fleeting thought of her former childhood friend resurfaced in her mind. Why did she think of him just now? Miharu didn’t even know herself. Perhaps it was because the boy sleeping before her had the same name as her childhood friend.

After Miharu had been staring at Rio for a while, she breathed a gasp of realization.

Ah, he’s going to catch a cold like this! I’ll go get a blanket!

She headed towards her own room in a hurry. Less than a minute later, Miharu returned to the living room in a flurry of footsteps, carrying a blanket in her arms.

Miharu placed the blanket over Rio gently, careful not to wake him up. Since she had just used the blanket herself mere moments ago, it was still cozy with a lingering warmth.

I can’t just walk into Haruto’s room without permission, so it should be fine if he uses mine... Right...?

Miharu faltered briefly, but eventually decided to timidly place the blanket over Rio.

“There we go,” she said in a quiet voice, gently lowering the blanket. Rio’s eyes suddenly blinked open.

“Huh? Ah...” Miharu let out a surprised sound. She was leaning towards Rio, so their faces were staring at each other at an extremely close distance. The two of them froze, just like that.

“U-Umm. I was worried you’d be cold, so I got a blanket...” Miharu said in a high-pitched voice with a blush to her cheeks.

“O-Oh, I see. Thank you very much.” Rio nodded reflexively, pulling the blanket closer to him.

However, there was a strange warmth to the blanket that was just placed on him…. Almost as though it was used moments before it had been given to him. When Rio realized that fact, he glanced down at the blanket. Sure enough, it wasn’t the one he usually used.

Huh? Could this possibly be Miharu’s…?

It had the same pattern as the blanket he had given to Miharu to use. Dumbfounded, Rio froze again.

“Umm, I’m going to make breakfast right now, so feel free to rest a little longer. Ah, or would you rather go back to your room to sleep?” Miharu asked; she didn’t seem particularly bothered, asking questions that showed more concern for Rio.

“No... I’m fine here,” Rio replied, promptly shaking his head. The warmth of the blanket was so comfortable, it seeped into his skin like a nostalgic memory, making him reluctant to part with it.

You ARE Wearing Them... Right?

One night, several days after Miharu and the others started living in the rock house...

After taking his bath, Rio returned to the living room. There, Miharu and Aishia were sitting next to each other on the couch, drinking tea. But when Rio saw Aishia’s appearance, his eyes widened in shock.

“Huh? Aishia, those clothes...”

“... It’s Haruto’s shirt.”

Indeed, Aishia was wearing Rio’s shirt.

“Umm, I know Ai-chan can make her own clothes, but she’s always wearing the same thing... So I told her it might be better if she had pajamas to sleep in, and she came back wearing your clothes,” Miharu explained nervously.

“Ahaha, I see...” Rio gave a strained smile of understanding, then looked at Aishia.

“It’s comfortable.” Aishia raised both her arms and flapped them to show off the shirt.

“Maybe we should buy some clothes for Aishia after all? Even though she said she didn’t need any the first time we went shopping... What do you think, Miharu?”

“Umm, I was surprised when her clothes suddenly disappeared when we went to take a bath. And what happens when she’s asleep or unconscious? Will that be okay?”

“Aah, I see...” At Miharu’s hesitant words, Rio smiled guiltily, trying to mask his thoughts. He had recalled the time when Aishia had crawled into his bed completely naked.

“Come to think of it, what would happen if Ai-chan took off her usual clothes?” Miharu asked Aishia as the thought suddenly crossed her mind.

“They disappear if they leave my side,” Aishia replied plainly.

“I-I see...” Miharu nodded, slightly bewildered.

“Haruto, can I sleep wearing this today?”

“I don’t mind if you wear it, but... don’t you sleep in your spirit form?”

If she was in her spirit form, she wouldn’t be able to wear any clothes.

“I’m sleeping with Miharu today.”

“Ah, I see. Then... it should be fine, I think? I guess it’s almost like a one-piece dress...” Rio nodded in confusion, looking at Aishia’s frame.

Because she was wearing a men’s shirt, the size was completely wrong; it was in danger of falling off at any moment. Not to mention the abnormally large amount of exposed skin on the lower half of her body.

It was all such a sight for sore eyes. Rio averted his gaze awkwardly.

“Ai-chan, I can lend you my clothes instead?” Miharu questioned; she must have had a similar thought to Rio.

Aishia shook her head bluntly. “I’m fine.”

“Haha,” Rio laughed dryly. Miharu also found herself at a loss for words.

“I’m starting to get sleepy.”

With a small yawn, Aishia heavily slumped over the sofa. Her appearance was so defenseless, that sure enough, her shirt fell loose.

Miharu tried to get Aishia to sit up in a fluster. “Ai-chan, you’ll catch a cold if you sleep here. Shall we go to my room...?!” Suddenly, her gaze was drawn to the shirttail that was only barely covering Aishia’s exposed rear, and she choked on her words.

“...Miharu?” Rio asked Miharu quizzically.

“Haruto!” Miharu called in a hurry.

“Y-Yes?”

“Y-You didn’t see, right?!” she asked frantically.

“Huh? Uh, right.” Unsure of what was going on, Rio cocked his head in confusion.

“Thank goodness…” Miharu sighed in relief, before making Aishia sit up in a hurry. “A-Ai-chan, get up!”

“Mm...” Aishia sat up languidly.

Miharu took a deep breath. “Umm, Ai-chan. You are wearing them... right?” she asked in a quiet and shy voice.

“...Wearing what?”

“Um... your underwear.”

“Nope.” Aishia shook her head calmly.

“Wha—?! T-That’s no good! You’re a girl! What if Haruto sees you?!” Miharu yelled, her face completely pale.

“I don’t mind if it’s Haruto, though.” Aishia looked at Rio and inclined her head curiously.

Miharu was utterly shaken. “Y-You have to mind! Geez! Haruto, can we take Aishia shopping tomorrow?!” she asked, turning to Rio.

“Y-Yes, let’s go. As soon as possible.” Rio nodded with debilitating embarrassment.

Welcome Home, Master

One day, Rio opened the door to his rock house —

“Welcome home, master.”

— with Miharu standing there, greeting him with a springy voice and an adorable smile.

“M-Miharu...?” Rio’s eyes widened with dumbfounded surprise.

Miharu was wearing what could only be described as a maid outfit; she elegantly pinched the classic long skirt with her fingertips. After Rio remained frozen, she looked up at his face.

“Umm, is something the matter, Master? Have I made an error somewhere?” she asked worriedly.

Rio shook his head, his voice coming out flustered. “Huh? Ah, no, you’re not lacking in anything! There’s no way you could!”

“Thank goodness,” Miharu said with a sigh of relief. “But, Master... are you feeling well? Your face seems rather red... Ah, please excuse me.” She stared at Rio’s face closely, then hesitantly reached a hand out to his cheek.

Rio flinched. “Huh?!”

“Umm, Master... I think you may have a fever after all. I’d like to check properly... Will you bend over a little? I’m too short to reach...” Miharu stretched upwards as much as she could in front of Rio, looking apologetic as she spoke.

“Y-Yeah, sure.” Rio promptly bent his knees and lowered the position of his face, so that Miharu was able to place her forehead against Rio’s.

“...You really do have a fever,” she murmured anxiously.

“N-No, this isn’t a fever. Ah, but I may indeed be feverish right now...” Rio denied it in a haste, then tried to come up with an explanation.

“Master, you should lie down immediately. I’ll do my best to nurse you to full health! Master is always working so hard... Don’t you think you deserve to rest for today?” Miharu asked enthusiastically, then tightly grabbed Rio’s hand.

“Huh...? Ah, yes.” Unable to meet Miharu’s eyes, Rio stared down at their clasped hands as he nodded nervously.

“Ah, I-I’m sorry. I touched Master with too much familiarity...” With a red face, Miharu apologetically let go of Rio’s hand, but he reached for her hand back.

“N-No, that’s not true! Could you take me to my bedroom?” he asked.

“Y-Yes, of course.” Miharu’s cheeks flushed even more as she agreed with a bashful smile. She led him to his bedroom, her hand still in his.

Miharu made Rio sit on his bed. “Master... I’ll wipe your sweat for you, so would you please remove your clothes?” she offered.

Rio was taken aback. “Eeh?! N-No, that’s asking for too much...” he said disapprovingly.

“N-No, this is my job! That is, umm... unless you don’t want it?” Despite Miharu gathering up her courage to protest, the last part of her question was asked with caution.

Rio nodded hesitantly. “...Umm, only if you don’t mind, then.”

Miharu shook her head. “I don’t mind at all! I’m happy to do so! Because I...! Ah, no, umm...” However, she lost her momentum in the middle of her exclamation and ducked her head in embarrassment.

“...Miharu?” Rio said, watching her expression carefully.

“Ah, no. It’s nothing. Ehehe... I should get to wiping your sweat already.” Miharu smiled shyly, then shook her head to dismiss the topic.

Rio nodded hesitantly once more. “...All right.”

Isn’t Miharu acting a little weird today? ...Wait, what’s more weird is the situation right now! Why has Miharu become my maid?!

Snapping back to his senses with a gasp, Rio writhed his entire body in agony. Suddenly, he could feel his consciousness rapidly coming to.

“...Huh?!” Rio sprung up from where he lay in bed. He opened his eyes with a blink and his vision suddenly changed to the familiar sight of his bedroom.

For some reason, Aishia was standing right next to him, wearing the same maid outfit that Miharu had been wearing.

“Good morning, Master,” she said, inclining her head.

...So it was a dream. I must be tired.

Rio’s face twitched as he sighed and fell back against his bed. His mind gradually grew hazy once more.

“Good night, Master?” he thought he heard a voice say.

Your Red Cheeks are because of the fever, right?

On a day roughly two weeks after Miharu, Aki, and Masato began living with Rio, Miharu had exerted herself too much trying to get used to her new life and came down with a fever.

Rio noticed something was wrong with her expression as they were making breakfast, then immediately checked on her condition and sent her to rest in her room.

He handed Miharu a mug filled with elven-made medicine. “It’s probably a cold. If you take this medicine and rest, your fever should go down by nightfall. You should stay in this room and relax.”

“...Okay. I’m sorry,” Miharu apologized with a reddened face.

“What are you apologizing for?” Rio asked with a soft smile.

“Umm, for causing you trouble...”

“You’re no trouble at all, Miharu. You’re working your hardest -- if anything, you’re working toohard. You’re even doing over half the housework.”

“That’s just my job...” she said gloomily.

“Hmm, maybe I’ve been putting too much of a burden on you.” Rio smiled wryly.

Miharu shook her head in a hurry. “N-No, not at all. If anything, we’re causing all the burden for you, Haruto.” She knew that Rio had been cutting back on his sleeping hours in order to make more learning material for their language lessons.

“I don’t consider it a burden at all. Actually, I’m having quite a bit of fun.”

“Then, so am I.”

“Ahaha... I’m happy to hear you say that. Well, let’s focus on getting you back to full health for now. Please leave the housework to me today.”

“...Okay. I appreciate it.” Miharu still seemed rather apologetic, as she faltered for a moment before agreeing.

“Just leave it to me.”

Rio nodded kindly, then left the room quickly to allow Miharu to rest quietly. Once the door closed with a click, Miharu was left by herself.

She looked around. Miharu was rarely ever in her room other than to sleep, so it was a new feeling that left her somewhat restless. Or, perhaps it was because she couldn’t calm down if she wasn’t doing housework. And so, she remained in a state of distress for a while, until a knock reverberated on her door.

“Come in... A-Ai-chan?”

Once Miharu gave permission for entry, the door opened to reveal Aishia carrying a bucket and cloth.

“Good morning, Miharu. Your fever okay?”

“Yup, I’m fine.” Miharu nodded cheerfully.

“I’ll nurse you… Wipe your sweat away,” Aishia offered to take care of Miharu.

“Umm... I’m fine, though?”

“You don’t need... nursing?”

Aishia peered at Miharu’s face as though to confirm if she was really okay.

“Ah... umm. Then, can I ask you to wipe my sweat away?” Miharu felt the need to respond to Aishia’s sincerity and nodded in a slight fluster.

“Got it. Then, strip.” With a single nod, Aishia walked towards where Miharu was lying in the bed.

“O-Okay.” Miharu nervously stripped herself of her top.

“Show me your back.”

“Okay.” Miharu followed Aishia’s orders and turned her back around shyly. Immediately, a cool hand towel made contact with her back.

“Eek?!” Miharu flinched.

“Is it cold?” Aishia took the cloth away from her body, but Miharu shook her head with a strained laugh.

“I-It’s fine. I was just surprised at how sudden it was.”

“I’m going to continue, then.”

“Please do.”

Aishia started to wipe Miharu’s back once more with the wet cloth, but Miharu let out a ticklish sound.

“Mmh... ah.”

“You okay?” Aishia’s hand stopped once more.

“Y-Yup. But could you wipe a little more slowly? Ahaha.”

“Got it.” Obeying Miharu’s request, Aishia resumed wiping Miharu’s back.

“Ngh...”

Aishia’s hand moved in a rather bold way, reaching straight for all the risky spots directly. Though her wiping speed had slowed, it actually made her feel more flustered, as it had steadily stimulated Miharu’s skin.

However, Miharu felt guilty for continuing to speak up, so she endured it. Then, another knock of the door echoed through the room, but Miharu was so focused on staying calm that she didn’t notice the sound.

Aishia, who heard the sound clearly, stood up instead.

“Huh? What’s wrong, Ai-chan?” The sudden halt of Aishia’s hand made Miharu look up in question.

“A knock. Haruto’s here,” Aishia informed her shortly, before striding over to the door to open it.

“...Huh? Huh?!”

Miharu raised her voice in confusion and looked over at the door. There stood a dumbfounded Rio, frozen with a tray of food he had made for her. Rio and Miharu both watched each other in a state of shock, their faces gradually reddening.

“I-I’m sorry!” they both apologized together. Miharu covered her body with her blanket in a panic. Rio also averted his eyes as fast as humanly possible, then retreated to the living room with rapid speed.

That night, after Miharu’s fever had completely gone down, her cheeks would redden every time she looked at Rio’s face, making Aki and Masato worry about her.

Chapter 6: Shopping

After he ate, Rio called Aishia to join him outside so that he could speak to her alone.

It was the perfect day to go shopping: the weather was clear, and a refreshing wind gently ruffled the grassy fields.

Rio stretched lightly and relaxed. “You can fly with spirit arts, right? Do you have an elemental specialty?” he asked.

As a spirit — the progenitor of spirit arts — Aishia would naturally know spirit arts, too. With spirit arts, a caster or spirit usually had their own specialty element. Experienced casters and high-ranked spirits could all use a certain level of every element, so Rio assumed Aishia could fly as well.

“Yup, I can fly. My specialty is the same as Haruto. I’m proficient in all of them,” Aishia confirmed quietly.

“...I see. I’ve heard that universal users are really rare before, though.”

Universal spirit arts users and spirits were few and far between. Because Rio himself was one of those exceptional users, he didn’t show that much surprise other than the slight widening of his eyes.

“That’s why I can fight, too. I can protect Haruto. I can stay beside Haruto,” Aishia suddenly said.

“Aishia...” Rio’s eyes widened further this time, murmuring Aishia’s name.

“You can lean on me whenever you need me. Just say the word, Haruto.”

Rio’s eyes widened at Aishia’s words, and he gave a soft smile. “...Thank you. I may need to leave the house in the near future. When that time comes, could I leave Miharu’s protection in your hands, Aishia? Of course, I doubt you’d need to do anything as long as you’re all in this house.”

“Okay,” Aishia agreed quietly but dependably.

“Also, we’re going to go shopping today. Could I ask you to accompany Miharu and act as her interpreter while we’re out?”

“Yup, sure.”

“...Thank you.” Rio thanked Aishia with an even more peaceful smile on his lips. She was so obedient and earnest, he couldn’t help but feel sorry for her.

“Is that all?” Aishia wondered, tilting her head.

“Mm, I actually wanted to try flying in the air together, but could I check your fighting capabilities instead? We won’t be using any flashy spirit arts, though... Can you fight at close range?” Rio asked. Their conversation just now had piqued his curiosity about how well a humanoid spirit like Aishia could hold their own in battle.

“I can.”

“Then, let’s do some light sparring. We have to go shopping soon, so let’s keep it short.”

“All right.”

“Okay. When this rock hits the floor, the match begins. Are you ready?” Rio picked up a rock, then placed 15 meters of distance between Aishia and himself.

“Yup.” Aishia gave a short nod.

Once Rio confirmed her nod, he gently threw the rock upward. The rock drew a parabolic line through the air before landing on the ground.

Immediately after, Aishia disappeared.

In actuality, Aishia had moved in front of Rio in an instant. At the same time, her arm reached out to grab him by his clothes.

So fast! A throwing technique, huh? Rio’s eyes opened wide in shock before his hands moved reflexively. He broke out in a cold sweat, and he evaded Aishia’s hands while backstepping.

He had underestimated her; Rio had unknowingly categorized Aishia as someone that needed to be protected. However, Aishia had blown his naivety away at a moment’s notice, as though she was proving her own strength to him.

Aishia closed the gap between them with determination, launching a skillful attack. With a combination of feints, her fists and feet moved at Rio at a terrifying speed. The force behind a single hit would be enough to damage his enhanced body if it made clean contact.

However, Rio was still able to smoothly evade every attack.

There’s something familiar about the way she moves... Wait, is she copying my moves?! he thought, seeing that Aishia’s close-range combat techniques were consistent with his own style. While he wasn’t sure of the reason, it was possible that she had learned the same techniques as him through osmosis, just like when it came to his language.

For several moments, Aishia continued to launch her attacks at Rio, before suddenly changing her attack pattern. She backed away for a moment and put distance between them, then used wind spirit arts — just like Rio — to accelerate her movement, stirring up the surroundings as she took off again.

With a deep breath, Rio mustered a large amount of ode from within himself to raise the effect of his physical enhancement and sharpen his senses even more. As Aishia closed in on him, Rio was only barely able to perceive Aishia’s movements with his sharpened senses. Suddenly, Aishia thrust the palm of her hand at him, but Rio flanked her and sidestepped her outreached palm at the same time. He then aimed to trip Aishia off balance and used that momentum to lightly fling her in the direction she was moving. Aishia’s eyes widened, but she gracefully flipped over in midair to deftly land on the ground, then turned to resume attacking once more.

“W-Wait! That’s enough, Aishia! I have a good idea of your ability now!” Rio called out. Aishia froze on the spot.

“...I couldn’t land a single hit. You dodged them all,” she murmured quietly.

“Umm, well, they were all movements I knew already... So you could say I’ve been learning longer than you?” Rio replied with a wry smile. He didn’t know how much actual experience Aishia had on the battlefield; all he knew was that she was asleep for the last several years. It wouldn’t be strange for her skills to be dulled, even if she was a spirit.

“Haruto really is strong.”

“Ahaha, thank you. We shouldn’t be too late, so let’s hurry back inside the house.” Thus, Rio and Aishia went back inside.

◇◇◇

After his sparring match with Aishia, Rio prepared to depart for Amande.

“All right, we’ll be going now. You’ll be safe as long as you’re in this house, but we’ll try to hurry back soon anyway. Make sure you stay inside,” Rio said to Aki and Masato, who were left in charge of the house.

The house was fortified and difficult to physically break into once it was locked and secured, and it was covered by a compact version of the barrier around the spirit folk village, so most outside intruders would never even step within the range of the barrier. Unless a formidable enemy just happened to pass right by the house, it was most likely safe. The surrounding area was devoid of people and the grasslands had very few monsters, so there was a very low probability of a fierce opponent passing by.

“Yeah, we got it. Take care of Miharu, Haruto.”

“Please be careful on your trip.”

Masato and Aki spoke up as they saw them off.

“I’ve left a lunch that can be eaten cold on the dining table for you, just make sure you heat up the miso soup. You know how to heat it, right?” Miharu asked worriedly.

“We’ll be fine. You’ve taught us plenty of times already.”

“How many times has it been, Miharu? Just go already!” They both responded to Miharu’s overprotectiveness with wry smiles.

“Let’s go, Miharu,” Rio urged.

“Okay...” Miharu agreed reluctantly. “We’ll be back soon.”

“But can you really make it back today? It looks like we’re completely surrounded by plains... Is the city actually really nearby or something?” Masato asked curiously.

“Come to think of it, I haven’t told you how we’re going. I’ll show you something interesting. Come outside for a bit, you two,” Rio said, leaving the living room to head for the front door. Aishia immediately followed him, and the other three slowly made their way over, too.

Once they left the house, a vast area of grassy plains spread before them outside.

“...It really is an amazing view,” Miharu murmured, overwhelmed by the view of the land that stretched all the way to the horizon. Now that a full day had passed, the feeling that she was in another world really cemented in as she looked out at the scenery. Aki and Masato hummed in admiration as well.

“You’re about to see something much more amazing,” Rio said with a faint smile tugging at his lips.

“Even more than this?” Miharu turned her head hesitantly, unable to imagine how that would be possible.

Instead of answering Miharu, Rio addressed Aishia who had been standing silently. “Aishia. I want to see how far you can fly, so can you show me?”

“Sure.” Aishia nodded gently. Then, her legs began to float off the ground. She continued to rise up easily, as though ignoring the force of gravity.

“Huh? ...Huh? Wha?” Miharu and the others were taken aback, staring up at the ascending Aishia in shock. She had already risen far up into the sky, moving about freely through the air at quite a fast speed.

She said she could use all types of spirit arts, but I guess that was to be expected of a humanoid spirit. Rio watched Aishia’s figure in admiration.

In the meantime, Masato returned to his senses. “Wow! Is that sorcery too?!” he asked excitedly.

“It’s different from sorcery, but you can think of it as something similar for now. I’ll explain the particulars another time,” Rio answered simply. A proper explanation would require much more time.

Just then, Aishia descended softly toward the ground.

“Well?” she tilted her head and asked Rio in a monotonous voice after she had smoothly landed.

“It’s perfect — I have no complaints. Sorry to say this just as you landed, but shall we go now? Are you ready too, Miharu?” Rio smiled and nodded at Aishia before turning to look at Miharu.

With a flinch, she stepped forward hesitantly. “Y-Yes. Please lead the way.”

“...It might be a bit late asking this now, but are you comfortable with heights?” Rio asked carefully.

“I’m okay with them... I think.” Miharu nodded, though in a slightly nervous manner. She had never flown through the air like that before, so all she could do was make an assumption.

“I guess we’ll have to find out once we’re up there. We’ll fly slowly at first.”

“Yes, please.”

Rio called for Aishia, but when he looked around she was nowhere to be seen. “Aishia... Huh?”

He had wanted her to carry Miharu instead, since he figured it would be better than having someone of the opposite gender do it, but...

“If you’re looking for Aishia, she left already,” Masato said, pointing at the sky; Aishia was already quite far up. She seemed to be warming up for the flight, as she showed no signs of coming back down.

“Haha... Erm, do you mind if I’m the one that goes with you?” Rio asked Miharu nervously with a dry laugh.

Miharu nodded with curiosity. “Huh? No, I’m fine with that.” She had yet to realize what Rio was being self-conscious about.

“Umm, I’ll have to carry you...” Rio admitted with difficulty, and Miharu finally understood.

“A-Ah, I see. That’s right.” Her cheeks turned bright red with embarrassment.

“Ahaha, maybe not after all. I’ll call Aishia back and get her to carry you.” Rio laughed somewhat awkwardly and brushed it off, preparing to move upward and call Aishia back down. However, not wanting to be rude to Rio, Miharu spoke up in a fluster.

“N-No! I-It’s okay, I don’t mind!”

Rio turned back with a strained smile. “You don’t have to force yourself, you know?”

“I-It’s fine, really. I don’t mind at all, if it’s you. I trust you, so... please.” In a tumble of words, Miharu stopped Rio and bowed with embarrassment.

“...Umm... Then, excuse me.” After much contemplation, Rio decided that rejection here would be rude. He slowly approached Miharu in order to pick her up. With her acknowledgment, Rio nodded and picked her up, bridal-style.

“Umm, a-am I heavy?” Miharu asked with a bright red face.

“Not at all — you’re very light. Like a feather, as the saying goes.” Rio shook his head with a grin.

In reality, Miharu was dainty and light. She had a soft, feminine body that Rio inadvertently felt through her clothes, despite the fact that she was wearing a thick outer coat — borrowed from Rio — over her uniform. To be honest, Rio was struggling quite a bit internally, but he desperately feigned composure to avoid being distracted by her body.

“I’ll focus on flying as safely as possible, but make sure you hold on tight anyway.”

“O-Okay,” Miharu nodded with a squeak, clinging to Rio timidly. She leaned her weight into him gently and clutched at his clothes. Their faces were almost close enough to touch.

Rio purposefully tore his gaze away from Miharu to speak to Aki and Masato standing to the side. “We’ll be off, now. Make sure you lock up properly.”

“Right. Let me fly when you get back!” Masato waved his hands with a carefree laugh.

“...Please take care of Miharu.” Aki bowed her head while keeping a close eye on their faces, having sensed the peculiar atmosphere flowing between the two of them.

Rio gave a faint smile and nod before kicking off from the ground and rising into the air. The sight of Aki and Masato’s figures on the ground grew smaller and smaller.

“Waaah, it’s amazing.” Miharu ogled at her surroundings as she tightened her grip on Rio.